<u> nicolaschang199@gmail.com</u>

• 1340 Pasqualito Dr | San Marino | CA , 91108, United States

+1 626 467 3805

Details

Driving license Date of birth F1942014 1991 / 01 / 10

Profile

A React & Solidity Engineer who has been working as a professional web & blockchain developer more than 7 years, most proficient at frontend & smart contract development using **React & Solidity & Web3**.

Always produced and built **optimized**, **user friendly** web pages with great performance and rich user experience using **React**, **Next**, **Angular and Typescript**.

Also I have built **NFT**(minting & staking) smart contract with gas optimization using **Solidity**, **ERC721**, **ERC721a**, **ERC1155**, **ER Web3**.

From time to time got involved in full stack developer roles and once was in responsible of some kind of **leadership** as well.

Using **MERN** stack, I have done some kind of small projects totally by myself.

That surely improved my backend and full-stack development skills and experience.

My skills in terms of backend and full stack development would be **Javascript**, **Node**, **GraphQL**, **MongoDB**, **MySQL**, **PHP** and **PHP frameworks** like **Laravel** or **CI**.

However, my mainly work is still focused on **frontend** & **smart contract** development particularly using **React** and **Solidity**.

In conclusion, my strongest skills are **Javascript** / **React** / **Node** / **Typescript** / **GraphQL** / **AWS** / **Solidity** / **Web3**.

Links

<u>Linkedin</u> <u>Github</u> <u>Portfolio</u>

1	โลกดีบลดีคร			

English Chinese Skills React Solidity Next NFT (ERC721, ERC721a, ERC1155) Redux Defi Gatsby Web3

Jest	Node		
Git	Express		
Docker	Laravel		
JIRA	PostgreSQL		
AWS	MongoDB		
WebSocket	GraphQL		

Education

Bachelor, Jiangxi University of Science & Technology, Ganzhou, Jinagxi

2011 - 2015

- Was a member of a basket ball team
- Specialty was the computer science
- Studied web development and walked through online courses

Employment History

React & Solidity Engineer, Velog, Seoul

January 2020 — July 2022

- Developed new **user-facing features** using React.js
- Developed Wulfz and TribeX NFT smart contract and did web3 integration.
- Developed **Takaprotocol Defi** smart contract and built **graphQL subgraph** similar with uniswap v3 subgraph.
- Built **reusable components** and **front-end libraries** for future use
- Optimized components for maximum performance across a vast array of web-capable devices and browsers
- Worked together with an engineering team, a designer and a project manager to achieve the **goals of the application**
- Estimated tasks accordingly based on your past experience
- Provided **help** and **guidance** to other engineers on the project
- Monitored and improving front-end performance

Frontend Developer, TopicPro, Chicago

November 2017 — December 2019

- Did plan, design, build, and implement the **user interface systems** of websites, software programs, and web-based applications
- Provided a satisfactory **user experience** with no issues, errors, or downtime
- Created and Optimized systems, played an active role in testing and troubleshooting, and resolved issues such as those related to accessibility and browser compatibility
- Often **served** as an intermediary bridging the **gap** between the user and the backend developers, and tweak tools and platforms to adapt to real-world use situations
- Reviewed and debugged code
- Developed **fully functional web applications** that align with business objectives.

- Followed the **best practices** in developments and **improved** them.
- Created high resolution **mockups** to **test interfaces** with users.

Freelancer on Upwork.com

April 2015 — October 2017

- Did freelancing on Upwork.com, Freelancer.com.
- Worked with almost 50 clients from all over the world, did full-stack development mostly using MERN Stack.
- Developed front end website architecture.
- Developed back-end website **applications**.
- Created servers and databases for functionality.
- Ensured **cross-platform optimization** for mobile phones.
- Ensured **responsiveness** of applications.
- Worked alongside **graphic designers** for web design features.
- Saw through a project from **conception** to **finished** product.
- · Designed and developing APIs.
- Met both technical and client needs.

Typical Project

https://wulfznft.com

Wulfz are the Genesis collection of the Wulfz ecosystem. When staked, Wulfz earn 10 \$AWOO. \$AWOO is the token to the entire Wulfz ecosystem. \$AWOO can be used to redeem whitelist spots, train (animate) your Wulfz, mint upcoming Werewulfz, mint Wulfz VX, and more. It is sold out within 3 mins since public mint is started and trading on opensea was very active. I have built Wulfz (minting & staking) smart contract and Minting page, Web3 integration.

https://apkpure.com/lolly-chat-with-idols-old/com.myfans

Powerlook is one of the fastest-growing e-commerce brands in India which offers a unique range of men's casual wear with a shade of western touch.

Powerlook is a family-owned business that started its first retail shop in 2010.

They have three retail shops in Andheri. Borivali and Thane in Mumbai.

In this project, I was in charge of frontend development using React and Emotion.

https://bondlingo.tv

BondLingo is an online platform that offers more than 500 lecture videos and hundreds of JLPT problems to assist people to learn Japanese. It also provides features for users to feel free to create their own problem sets or movies. The client requested us to establish a platform where people can acquire the Japanese language. The integrated Mobile App needs to enhance creativity and make teachers gain self-confidence in creating and distributing every lesson plan. To suit the client's requirements, our team of 9 developers built a web-based solution and mobile app utilizing some technologies such as NodeJS, WordPress, and ReactJS. I took part in this project as a React JS developer.

References

Jonathan Lee from Spokes Digital

jonathantodev421@gmail.com